Oh well, honor for all
Of the big and the small
Well, the taller they stand
Well, the harder they fall
We live for today
But we die for the next
With blood in our veins
And the air in our chests
So we step into war
With our hearts on the line
The dirt on our boots
It shakes free over time
The music it fades
The violin slows
The darkness it rises
As the sun goes
Love is a distant aroma at best
A withering smile that's
Stuck deep in your vest
The night air it wraps
Its fingers around
Your body it shakes from
A now distant sound
Oh, the sound of her voice
A sweet symphony
Played over and over
Until you are free
The music it fades
The violin slows
The darkness it rises
As the sun goes
Can you feel the
New day rising
Climbing up the
East horizon
They can't hold us
Down we'll fight through
Each and every
One will start new
Well, we shall not stumble
No, we shall not fall
We shall not crumble
No, we shall stand tall
Well, death it will come
As sure as the night
But we will not run
No, we live but to fight
Oh, with blood on our hands
And dirt on our knees
We tear at the ones
Who brought the disease
The music it fades
The violin slows
The darkness it rises
As the sun goes
Can you feel the
New day rising
Climbing up the
East horizon
They can't hold us
Down we'll fight through
Each and every
One will start new
Can you feel the
New day rising
Climbing up the
East horizon
They can't hold us
Down we'll fight through
Each and every
One will start new